<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>About Us on DataForNerds</title><link>https://datafornerds.io/about-us/</link><description>Recent content in About Us on DataForNerds</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 16:12:33 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://datafornerds.io/about-us/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How does this work?</title><link>https://datafornerds.io/about-us/how-does-it-work/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 16:12:33 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://datafornerds.io/about-us/how-does-it-work/</guid><description>The Scripts The entire process starts with a script that collects the data in its current, less-than-usable, format and convertings the data into JSON. These scripts are stored in our GitHub repository under the scripts folder. When the script runs, it outputs the data into the content folder within the repository.
The GitHub Actions We&amp;rsquo;re fortunate the GitHub has provided an easy way to run PowerShell scripts on a scheduled basis using PowerShell Core running on Ubuntu.</description></item><item><title>Terms of Use</title><link>https://datafornerds.io/about-us/terms-of-use/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 16:12:33 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://datafornerds.io/about-us/terms-of-use/</guid><description>The Data (JSON Files) Ultimately, you are free to do whatever you wish with the data, so long as it doesn&amp;rsquo;t violate any of the rights of the creators of the data (e.g. Microsoft). You can manipulate it and even remove the DataForNerds header that we put at the top. If you use the data in any of your projects, it would be awesome if you attributed us, but it&amp;rsquo;s not required.</description></item><item><title>Who is DataForNerds?</title><link>https://datafornerds.io/about-us/about-us/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 16:12:33 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://datafornerds.io/about-us/about-us/</guid><description>Our Origin Story DataForNerds.io was started in July of 2021 by Chris Kibble who was hopeful there would eventually be an easily queryable list of Windows 10 Releases for his SQL and PowerBI reports that mapped the installed version (e.g. build 19041 is actually commercially referred to as 20H1). When that didn&amp;rsquo;t happen he just decided to do it himself.
Contributers Chris Kibble Chris started DataForNerds.</description></item></channel></rss>